### Contact

nv251199@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nv251199 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

React.js

Node.js

**MERN Stack** 

### Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Professional Working)

#### Certifications

Create and Manage Cloud Resources

ReactJs, NodeJs, React Native

C-6477

Google Cloud Essentials

# Nitin Verma

Full Stack Developer | React JS | Node JS | MySql Gwalior

# Summary

Motivated student pursuing MCA degree backed by practical experience focused on full stack developer. Ready to improve knowledge and contribute to business success with organizational, project coordination, and administrative expertise. Proficient in working with React with Node Js as backend.

# Experience

Rootstechnology
Full Stack Developer
February 2022 - Present (6 months)

Numeric Infosystem Pvt. Ltd. Intern April 2021 - December 2021 (9 months) Gwalior, Madhya Pradesh, India

# Education

ITM University Gwalior India

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Software and Media

Applications · (2020 - 2022)

GOVT. SHRIMANT MAHAVRAO SHINDHIYA ADARSH SCIENCE COLLEGE

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2017 - 2020)